You can add a new empty table to your database with the create table command.
你可以使用创建表格命令 向数据库中添加新的空表格
When you create a table, you'll give the name of the table, and the names and
在创建表格时 你需要对 表格以及表格中每一列
the types of each column.
的名称和类型进行命名
You can also set constraints on each column and on the row as a whole.
你也可以对每一列 和所有行设置约束
We'll talk about constraints shortly, but for now, let's focus on types.
我们将很快讨论约束  现在重点讨论类型
Here's the simplest form of the create table command that doesn't have any
这是最简单的创建表格命令类型 没有任何约束 只有带有类型的列
constraints, only columns with their types, and gives the table a name.
并对表格进行命名
Now, we've dealt with text and integer types previously, and back in lesson
我们之前已讨论过文本和整数类型  现在回到第二课
two, I gave you a big, long list of lots and lots of types that SQL supports.
我曾向大家提供了一个包含大量 SQL 支持类型的长列表
The exact set of types that you can use will vary from system to system though.
但你实际可以使用的类型集 因系统不同而不同
If you're working with a database system that doesn't natively support the type
如果你使用的数据库系统 本身不支持所需类型
you need, there's usually a way to work around it.
通常有一种解决方法
For instance, PostgreSQL has a specific type for
例如  PostgreSQL 有某种特定类型的 IP 地址
IP addresses, but MySQL does not.
而 MySQL 却没有
MySQL programmers usually use an integer or a text string to store IP addresses.
MySQL 程序员通常会使用整数 或文本字符串来存储 IP 地址
Of the databases we've used in this course, PostgreSQL has a proper type for
关于我们在本课程中使用的数据库  PostgreSQL 具有合理的日期和时间类型
dates and times, but SQLite actually just stores dates as strings.
而 SQLite 实际上只是将日期存储为字符串
Database systems will often give you shortcuts to declare a particular
数据库系统 会经常提供用于
kind of column.
声明特定列的快捷方式
For instance, in PostgreSQL, you can have a column that stores the time and
例如 在 PostgreSQL 中  你的列可以存储时间和日期
date along with the time zone so
以及时区
you can do comparisons of data recorded in different places around the world.
这样 你就可以对记录的世界各地 不同地区的数据进行比较
The full SQL standard name for that column type is timestamp with time zone,
这种类型的列的完整 SQL 标准名称 是 timestamp with time zone
but PostgreSQL let's us abbreviate it as timestamptz.
但通过 PostgreSQL 可将其缩写为 timestamptz
Normally, if you're creating a database for a new application,
通常情况下 如果你正在为 新的应用程序创建数据库
you'll set up the database upfront as part of the installation procedure.
则需要事先将数据库 设为安装过程的一部分
It's technically possible to send create table commands from your app code, but
从技术上来讲 从你的应用代码发送 创建表格命令是可行的
it's usually a bad idea to do that outside of initial setup.
但在初始设置之外这样做 通常不是好主意
Your database design is really a part of your app's code.
数据库设计是 应用代码的一部分
It's just a part written in SQL instead of in Python.
它只是用 SQL 而不是 Python 编写的一部分
So, creating tables isn't like creating values in your program's variables.
因此 创建表格并不像 在程序变量中创建值
It's more like having your app rewrite its own code.
更像是让你的应用 重写其自己的代码
That's not something that's very common.
这种情况并不常见